http://accutechmarine.com/privacy-policy/

Information Collection and UseAccuTechMarine.com (“Us” or “We”) is the sole owner of information collected on this site to purchase most products and services from AccuTechMarine.com (refer to the next paragraph for the limited exceptions to this). We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations, order status updates, and to provide you with information on products and services that are available from us or parties associated with us. We may also use such information to better understand the shopping experiences of you individually or in conjunction with a group of our customers. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, & e-mail address. If you elect to receive our newsletter, surveys, or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items. However, if you elect not to receive newsletters, surveys, or special promotions, we may still periodically send other transactional communications to you that contain customer relationship information. This includes, for example, informational emails regarding changes in our policies, changes in our methods of conducting business, or requesting that you review the information we have on file for you or the options that you have previously selected regarding your transactions with us.We may also gather or receive information on you from third party sources, such as marketing databases made available for commercial purchase. Our use of such information will comply with applicable law, the limitations imposed by the third party on us in connection with our receipt of such information from such third party sources, but not necessarily this privacy statement. SessionsWe customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by session data. If you choose to reject the session, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the quoting system. The AccuTechMarine.com quoting system cannot function without sessions enabled so that the necessary information to process your request is retained. If you disable session data, AccuTechMarine.com will be unable to accept your online quote. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this session data with any third party.This privacy statement covers the use of session data by AccuTechMarine.com only and does not cover the use of session data by any advertisers. Log FilesWe use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. SharingWe may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes. Among such third parties are the three referenced immediately below.FedEx Corporation 942 South Shady Grove Road Memphis, TN 38120 1-800-GO-FEDEX www.fedex.comUPS Corporate Headquarters 55 Glenlake Parkway, NE Atlanta , GA 30328 United States www.ups.comUS Postal Service Headquarters 475 L’Enfant Plaza, SW Washington DC 1-800-ASK-USPS www.usps.comAs our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information i) as required by law, ii) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site, iii) when we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, iv) when we believe that your actions violate AccuTechMarine.com’s terms and conditions that you agree to by using, accessing or purchasing from or through www.AccuTechMarine.com (or its affiliated websites), v) when we believe that your actions violate any usage guidelines for specific products or services, vi) when we believe that your actions violate or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others, or (vii) when you consent to allow your personally identifiable information to be shared or disclosed.Finally, if you have elected to allow us to share your personally identifiable information at the time that you registered with us or provided us the information, or through a subsequent affirmative election through our website, we may later disclose such information to others in compliance with your election and this privacy statement. ChildrenAccuTechMarine.com does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use AccuTechMarine.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. AccuTechMarine.com is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children. LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that AccuTechMarine.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. Choice/Opt-outFor customers who wish to opt-out and stop receiving AccuTechMarine.com special offers, promotional materials, and newsletters, AccuTechMarine.com provides several ways to do so. Users who no longer wish to receive our special offers, newsletters or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by using the link provided in all AccuTechMarine.com communications to automatically unsubscribe. Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy you will not be notified. Last UpdateThe Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective 06-01-09.Please contact us for more information.  Friday 8am – 12pm © 2018 Accutech. All Rights Reserved. Website by High Effect Design Questions? Call Now
